designload.net 2010-06-20

# Privacy policy

_General_

By using our web site you acknowledge and agree that DesignLoad may change, amend, alter or replace any part of the privacy policy at any time, and that such changes, amendments, alterations or replacements shall be effective as of the time of posting of the amended privacy policy to the web site. You agree to regularly review this privacy policy for changes, amendments, alterations or replacements. If you do not agree with the changed, amended, altered or replaced privacy policy, do not acquire or license a product or service offered by DesignLoad and do not use or access the web site or information, material, products or services provided therein. If at any time you wish to withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure described herein of your personal information by DesignLoad, you may do so by contacting DesignLoad. 

_Personal information_

We use your personal information to enhance or evaluate the online service you receive. DesignLoad needs certain personal information if you wish to join our membership, receive our newsletter, or use certain services we provide at this web site. It is the policy of DesignLoad to not share or sell this information. 

We welcome your feedback regarding your online experience, our products and our service. We make every effort to respond quickly to all customer concerns. Please note, however, any questions, comments, feedback, suggestions, notes, messages, or other communication (collectively, the "Comments") sent to DesignLoad shall be and will remain the property of DesignLoad. 

_Use of personal information_

Personal information may include your personal contact information or your company contact information. DesignLoad will use this information in order to reply your inquiries, provide you with requested products and services or contact you regarding new products and services. 

By accessing the services or products of DesignLoad and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

_Law enforcement agencies_

DesignLoad fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies working to identify those who may use our services for illegal activity. Therefore, we reserve the right to disclose information to law enforcement agencies about members who we believe are violating our content guidelines or are involved in otherwise unlawful activities. 

_Children's online privacy_

DesignLoad is concerned with the safety of children when they use the Internet. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we receive actual knowledge that a child under the age of thirteen has contacted us without her or his parent or guardian's permission, we will remove all personal information about that person from our files.
